customers usually have to spend a lot of
time and effort on paperwork such as
documents printing and mailing forms
when dealing with claim submission it is
not easy to keep track of claims
progress after submission as well
Prudential will lead you to a new era of
claim submission with our new electronic
claim submission system he claims you
can use your desktop computer tablet or
smartphone to submit your claim
application check claim status and
receive instant approval notice anytime
anywhere
claim submission has become easier than
ever
other than enjoying your services on our
round-the-clock in claims platform you
will also receive a SMS message when
your claim is approved or if any pending
documents are required from today
onwards all you need is a smart device
and claim submission will be right at
your fingertips now let's take a look at
how we can submit claims easily through
each names with the help of different
devices to submit your claims online
please use your smartphone or tablet
because you need to sign on the
electronic forms to submit your claims
if you're using a desktop computer you
can save the information you entered for
future modification by clicking save any
time starting from the landing page of
my Prudential click on e claims and then
click start the claim
select medical benefit claim after
reading the claims procedures and the
claims documents checklist go see the
online application form first of all
select life assured
enter personal details and select which
benefits to claim if you did not pass
the claim form part two to your doctor
to fill in you can download it here then
select claim sequence it is a new claim
or further claim and provide reason for
this medical benefits claim whether it
is out of an accident or an illness
afterwards you may enter details of
consultation and hospitalization if you
apply for claims from other insurers or
organisations you will need to provide
relevant information we have different
methods of claims payment please choose
one finally you need to upload the
relevant document for claims application
you can take photos directly or upload
photos from the photo gallery the file
format should be JPEG PDF or tips each
file should not exceed 5 Meg then click
Next
in step 2 you can preview and confirm
the information you entered is accurate
scroll down and VP personal information
collection statement and declaration and
authorization at the bottom if you agree
please sign and submit
in step three you have completed the
submission successfully for us to grant
compensation as soon as possible please
send us the original medical receipt of
the relevant claim once the compensation
is granted you will receive a SMS
notification whether your claim is
submitted through e claims on my
credential or not you can check the
status of all claims at any time through
each lanes on the landing page of each
aims you may use life assured claims
number or data search records submitted
for example searching the submissions
within the last nine months you can
check the claim status of claim
submissions of all life assured during a
particular period you may also submit
additional documents at any time we'll
send a SMS to you when we require you to
submit additional documents by then you
can login to the platform select the
like the shorts name get to this page
and click you to see the required
additional information list then click
on submit document now
you can upload documents according to
the list please note that the five
format should be JPEG PDF or TIFF each
file should not exceed five Meg then
click Next
scroll down and read the personal
information collection statement and
declaration and authorization at the
bottom then click confirm and submit
your submission of additional document
is now completed if you have previously
saved claims information during the
application process you can return to
the landing page of my credential then
select saved records and you will see a
list of all the claims form saved by
clicking on the action button you can
return to the save record then you can
continue with the rest nowadays
convenient ease and high transparency
are of utmost importance to customer
service he claims the new electronic
claims submission system from Prudential
allows you to submit your claims and
receive timely notifications of your
claim status Anytime Anywhere claim
submission is as easy as it is
[Music]
you